How do you feel about the improvements
made? I guess the main thing is be a
better team in August than you were on
February 8th leaving the field. How do
you feel the progress on?
>> Yeah, I mean I I think that we're all
excited about the guys that we've added
and uh you know we we spent a lot of
time evaluating these guys uh scouts,
coaching staff, putting in work, trying
to find out about them as people,
finding any connections that we have.
And uh we feel like we're really
intentional trying to get the right kind
of people again. and um we were able to
you know come to agreements with these
guys and we're excited about you know
improving the team any way we can.
>> What went into moving away from Stefon?
>> Uh just a variety of factors looking at
um you know financials ability you know
a lot of things go into this um and we
have nothing but respect for Stefan. He
was an absolute warrior for us as I as I
said to him um multiple times after
games and uh just really appreciate all
his contributions to the team.
>> Was there any consideration of a new
contract with him or was it just you
guys were moving on?
>> Uh we talked about a variety of options
and uh ultimately just went in this
direction and you know decided excited
to move forward with the guys that we
signed today.
>> And like considering the year I mean he
had a pretty good year for you that
game.
>> Is there anything he could have done to
come back for a second year? Um,
I don't I'm not sure I know how to
answer that. I mean, we we you know, we
factor in a lot of different things and
ultimately we decided to to move forward
and we wish him nothing but the best and
you know, as we told him uh when we
spoke to him just, you know, and he was
super classy like as we told him anyway
we can help out, we will. If
>> Romeo didn't play a ton on the inside,
could you see him do you project him to
be someone who can do a little bit more
of that than maybe Green Bay let him do?
Uh, I think I think he has a a really uh
cool skill set. Um, I think he play
outside, inside, he blocks, he can play
Z, he can play X, he's good on the short
routes, he's good on the deep routes,
he's good with the ball in his hands.
Um, he's has a lot of route variance
that we liked and, uh, you know, strong
for the ball. There's some things that,
you know, he can improve upon that we'll
try to help him with, but uh, overall
just the competitor, the person. I mean,
I don't know if you guys saw him up
here, like he was already in the
playbook. He was he was he was on his
iPad learning the formations while we I
was trying to get him to sign his
contract this morning. So it was pretty
cool
>> with with him. Is it is it a
>> still want to do some more wide out will
the door be closed on maybe revisiting
stuff?
>> Uh I wouldn't say the door's closed. I
mean again we're going to look through
look through every way we possibly can
to to help improve the team
>> with with Romeo and Steph. Is it sort of
a one forone replacement
>> as far as
>> um you lose a lot of production with
Steph. He leaves enter Romeo. Do you
view that as all right, we don't have
Digs here, but to sort of replace him in
terms of the targets and
>> Yeah, I mean, I think it'll be a variety
of guys. You know, I think it'll, you
know, Steph moved around a lot in the
offense and we have some guys that that
are still here that we think can, you
know, do more. Kahan can certainly move
around more than he did last year. Matt
can play every position. and Kyle can
play every position and then you know
Pop when he was on the field this year
was very productive. So we feel good
about the group and you know the tight
end group's kind of part of that as
well. So you know we're excited to see
what Josh can put together for the
offense.
>> Speaking of Josh um you brought in
Reggie fullback and Josh is kind of
notorious for like the fullback in the
system. What stood out to you about him
that made you want to bring the game and
work with him?
>> Yeah, I mean when you watch just all his
plays um his his guy rarely makes the
tackle and you know he's light on his
feet. He can align multiple areas and
get in the hole. He's very square. Um
attacks people. Um likes blocking, very
good on special teams. Uh you know, he
only had two catches last year, so we're
hopeful that there'll be an uptick
there. But he does have good hands. So,
uh feel like he was a good addition.
>> With the wide receiver court, is this it
or could you be open to
>> uh again, we're always open to to trying
to improve the team any way we can? If
we see something out there that we think
can help us out, then we'll we'll look
towards it. ever in? Were you ever in on
Max Crosby?
>> Uh, we make a lot of exploratory calls
and, you know, I'll just leave it at
that.
>> What was your reaction to that deal
falling through?
>> Uh, you know, I didn't know too much
about it. Um, you know, I think I think
every team and general manager in the
league has to act in in in the faith of
what they think is best for their team.
and you know that one was maybe a little
unusual but um you know that's that's
their business.
>> Would you be opening to revisiting those
talks now backers
>> w with Max Crosby specifically? Um I'd
have to to talk to Richard Miller about
our numbers right now. Um so you know
again we'll we'll look into any player
that we think can help us
>> with Tucker.
>> Yeah, I mean that that's a that's a good
question. It's a it's a riskreward. We
just looked at, you know, we the the
film and the and the youth and the type
of injuries it was were all factors that
we talked about. Um, and just ultimately
we felt like, you know, taking a swing
at at a player that was still young and
had still has upside and is is a really
good player at his position.
>> How big of a factor was age when you
were looking at the roster from what who
walked off the field in the Super Bowl
to who you want to be next season and
even moving on from someone like Stefan?
Um, I mean it's a factor. We we look at
those things when we, you know, talk
about the length of a contract or, you
know, what type of upside does this
player have, but I wouldn't say it was
overly intentional that like, hey, we
need to get younger.
>> Elijah, do you view him playing left
guard and Jared going to center? How do
you kind of
>> I think that's probably the plan right
now. Um, you know, we we have some guys
that that do have versatility, which is
always a good thing, but I think that
would probably be the the plan at the
moment. Elliot, what appealed to you
guys about um Draymond Jones?
>> Uh Draymond has just been a good
football player at a variety of
positions throughout his career. Started
on the interior and has, you know, kind
of gotten smaller and moved outside. Um
he still has that alignment versatility
to play inside on third down. Um he can
set the edge. He's a good game rusher.
Um he's he's just, you know, one of
those guys that you just look at him and
there's not like a major weakness. He's
just a good football player. Do you look
at that edge spot as a place you could
still use a little help or you content
with what you have there?
>> Uh, I think I look at all the spots and
and try to see, you know, where we can
get better, what we can improve upon. I
think, you know, Edge Edge is no
different from a variety of other
positions where we think we need to, you
know, add something.
>> So, when you look at, you know, the team
that walked off the field in the Super
Bowl, I think at least one of the things
that maybe stood out to some people
stood out to me was obviously you guys
have a very good team, but maybe not
enough elite guys, game changers other
than Drake. the guys you sign in free
agency, obviously proven starters in the
NFL, but in your mind, where do the game
changers, the elite players, the
difference makers, come from on this
roster and this team?
>> Yeah, I mean, I I I think we have a
solid roster. I don't I don't know that
I'd necessarily agree that we don't have
really good players on this team,
difference makers. Um, you know, I would
say Vira Tucker in 2024 was one of the
best guards in the NFL. So, I don't know
if you could call a guard a
differencemaker, but, you know, he's
he's got a chance to do that. I think
Dobs is is really good. Draymond's
really good. Um, you know, I I I think
that, you know, we're doing everything
we can to help improve the team.
>> You can get very tough given that risk
reward. Could you talk about what Morgan
is someone to spend time with?
>> Yeah, definitely. Um, you know, we we
try to find out, use resources to try to
find out what kind of people these guys
are. Um, obviously having Morgan who
played next to him for a number of
years, uh, was was valuable and, um, you
know, I certainly probably think it
didn't hurt if if Vera Tucker had given
Morgan a call at some point to see what
we're all about because, you know, you
know, as much as as we're trying to find
out about the players, the players are
trying to find out about the culture of
the team. So, you know, those those
relationships work in both directions.
did happen. By the way, someone said
over there, how important it
>> Sorry,
>> how important it will it be um for last
year's rookie class, you know, several
of them in particular to take the next
step this season.
>> Yeah, I mean, I think it's huge anytime,
you know, we always talk about draft and
develop. I mean, you know, we had a
number of guys play a lot of snaps for
us, but anytime those guys can take a
next step to get to that next level, I
think is important. And you know, we we
have some guys that played a lot that
that certainly could improve upon some
things and we have some guys that maybe
didn't play as much that we're expecting
to take that next jump.
>> Obviously, you want to improve
everywhere, but it seems like there was
an emphasis in improving the ground
game. Is that fair to say? And how does
Julian Hill potentially factor into
that?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think I think there were
points in the season where we didn't run
the ball as well as we would have liked
last year uh for for a variety of
reasons. And I think adding, you know,
the fullback, a guard, and a and a tight
end who's primarily been a blocker in
his career, uh, you know, certainly was
intentional, uh, trying to get some
toughness and some identity guys for
coach Rabel in that offense. Um, Julian
is is a guy that obviously we've played
against and, you know, uh, played at a
smaller school and kind of, you know,
made the team as as an undrafted rookie
and, uh, you know, has really kind of
improved each year that he's been in it.
And you know, we think there's probably
still some meat on the bone in the
passing game as well for him, but
certainly a physical tough guy at the
point of attack.
>> There were a lot of reports and rumors
out there about the team having interest
in training for AJ Brown. Is is that a
situation you'd like to continue to
explore?
>> Uh again, we'll explore anything that we
think can help the team.
>> You still have a significant amount of
cap space. Is the priority now using
that cap space to sign for the agents or
have you started to focus a little bit
on future contracts renegotiations or
anything like that? Maybe
>> Yeah, I mean we've we've uh I mean it's
no secret we'd like to keep Christian
Gonzalez. Um and you know I don't know
what the timing of that is but that's
something that certainly we're preparing
for.
>> Very quickly after the season u coach
Rabel and you guys declared that Will
Campbell is the left tackle next year.
Why not take a little time to consider
all options? That's why I make that
decoration. So,
>> uh, you know, we know who the free
agents are going to be at left tackle.
We know who's in the draft at left
tackle. We know that we're picking 31st.
Um, and again, if you know, if there's
somebody that's a better left tackle
than Will Campbell that's that's
available, we'll look at anything. Um,
just not sure how realistic that is at
this time. There was a story going
around before the Crosby deal fell apart
that Tom Brady with the Raiders was not
interested in sending a player of the
caliber of Crosby to the Patriots. Is
there anything to your knowledge about
conversations or anything like that that
happened?
>> No. Um I I I'd be surprised if that was
true. Um, I have a really good
relationship with John Spitech, the
Raiders general manager, and you know,
we spoke speak about a variety of things
and that's never been a thing.
>> How wary are you do you have to be of
announcing deals before physicals are
done, things like that?
>> I mean, I think the way it's set up now
with the with the quote unquote
tampering window, probably less worried
about it, you I think I think it's good
to, you know, announce that you've
agreed to to terms with somebody just so
maybe other agents or other teams stop
calling them. Um, and also we actually
have to do that now in order to start
Nancy with the travel process. So that's
kind of the way it's set up to work now.
Yeah.
>> You mentioned the important of
versatility and safety, being able to do
a lot of different things live in
different places. Do you see Kevin Bard
in that more at this point in his
career? I know he played mostly deep
last year or is there maybe some
consideration to making sure that the
system kind of fits around him?
>> Yeah, I mean I I I you know I know he's
an older player. I haven't seen any real
drop off from him. Um I think he can
still do everything. Uh I think he
proved that last year. uh you know
obviously make an allp pro but uh you
know he's someone that that our coaching
staff has a ton of familiarity with and
you know they were I mean it was
ecstatic would be an understatement uh
when we were able to to agree to terms
with him. So um definitely think that he
still has the ability to play down play
back uh cover tackle all the things that
you need to do at safety. What's your
history with couple questions with with
Howie Roseman in terms of you know
players that maybe he has available like
AJ Brown? Is there a point is there like
a deadline where you just have to say
where you're building your team you just
have to kind of move on from from that
say the draft.
>> Uh I'm not I'm not sure I follow.
>> So the first question is what you know
your history with Harry Rose you have a
good relationship with John Spy. You
talk all the time. So I'm just curious
about that. And then in terms of
somebody like AJ Brown in the team
building process, is there a point where
you have to say, "Okay, this hasn't
happened by this point. If we're
interested in this player, we just have
to move on. We can't wait till June,
July, whatever."
>> Yeah, I mean, I I think uh number one, I
have a great relationship with Howie.
I've known him for a long time. Um they
actually put in a permission slip for me
uh when I was in Green Bay as a young
scout and uh that got blocked. But uh uh
so I' I've known Howie for a long time.
We have a good relationship. We talk,
you know, often. Um he's obviously a
great resource and someone you can learn
a lot from. Um and then as far as the
the deadline thing, I mean I I think I
think the only real deadlines you have
are, you know, sort of maybe salary cap
related is if you know,
for instance, did we spend money in free
agency that would take us out of
something else? Um but
uh I wouldn't say that there's a
deadline. Again, I'm trying to improve
the team. How rewarding is it over the
last two years to see this team go from
being a place that it might have been
difficult agency to look at now having
virtually every guy?
>> Yeah, I mean it's it's been tremendous
and you know I just have to have to
thank the crafts and have to thank Rael
and you know the culture that that
really has been instilled here for you
know really being responsible for that.
Drake as well. Um, you know, every free
agent kind of says the same thing. Want
to play for Rabel? Want to play with
Drake. I mean, it's it's pretty cool.
>> Did you spend too much money to be
involved with someone of a of a with a
bigger contract like say, I don't know,
the receiver in Philadelphia?
>> I'm not going to talk about a specific
player, uh, that's under contract with
another team. But, uh, we're h we're
happy with the guys that we signed and,
you know, we we think we've improved our
team.
>> Do you anticipate to be active in free
agency?
>> Say again. Do you anticipate continuing
to be active in free agency
>> like like now or next year? Oh,
>> uh again, we're still we're still
looking through everything. Um there's
there's still some quality players that
are available. So, if something makes
sense for us or, you know, someone comes
back to us and says, "Hey, you know, my
my market isn't what I thought it would
be," there there's always things that
we'll look at.
>> Thanks, guys.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. Thank you.